Contact

mariejanaee@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/marie-casillas-1b51871a5 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care Nursing Medical-Surgical Pediatrics

Certifications

Certification of Added Qualifications for Critical Care Medicine

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Dysrhythmia Course

Marie Casillas

Bachelors of Science and Nursing Graduate

Ontario, California

Summary

Experienced Emergency Room Technician with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Medical-Surgical, Emergency Medicine, Critical Care Nursing, Pediatrics, and Telemetry. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from West Coast University.

Experience

Cedars-Sinai
Emergency Room Technician
April 2017 - Present (3 years 4 months)
Los Angeles, California, United States

Emergency room technician at a busy level 1 trauma center in the heart of Los Angeles.

Kaiser Permanente Certified Nursing Assistant September 2015 - June 2019 (3 years 10 months) Anaheim, California, United States

Certified Nursing Assistant on Pediatrics, ICU, OB, Medical-Surgical Units, DOU, and telemetry floors.

LA VETA SURGICAL CENTER
PACU/Pre-Op Technician
February 2015 - February 2016 (1 year 1 month)
Orange, California, United States

Clinical work in both the recovery room and pre-op area.

Education

West Coast University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2018 - 2020)